嘿 J 怎么 你去哪了
Yo, J, what up, son, where you been?
没去哪 T 我不过想低调点
I ain't been nowhere, T. Just laying low, man.
现在注意 你会看到Darnell的小弟...
Now watch, you gonna see Darnell's little brother...
拿着洗衣篮出来
come on out with that laundry basket.
而钱就在洗衣篮里?
And the take's in the basket?
午后一次 晚上一次
Once in the afternoon, and one at night.
都用同一个洗衣篮
Always the same laundry basket.
你怎么知道的
How you know?
总得把那些钱运出来吧 伙计
That money got to come out somehow, man.
那我们就不用杀开一条血路冲上楼顶
So, we ain't got to blast our way to the top floor.
在街上等着他们送上门就好
We just wait till they're in the street with their shit.
今晚动手 听懂了吗
We gonna do them tonight, you heard?
入夜后
After it get dark.
和你说的一样
Just like you say.
马上把篮子放下 放下
Put the basket down now, put it down!
- 靠 我说了把篮子放下 - 放松 小姐 冷静
- Fuck, I said put the basket down! - Easy girl, chill.
你们这帮黑鬼 被逮个正着吧
You all niggers, you got caught slipping.
很遗憾事情会变成这样 宝贝 你们的屁股还挺性感的
Sorry it had to go down like this, baby, because your ass is cute.
但你们活该倒霉
But you got got.
漂亮 真漂亮
Nice, very nice.
贱货
Bitches!
这可不是你每天都看得到的
Now, that's something you don't see every day.
火线重案组 第二季 第三集 暗箭伤人
The Wire S02E03 Hot Shots
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"她们需要的是个工会"  ---Russell
不会英语
No English.
Kunta Kinte...
阿里巴巴 稀里哗啦
yabba dabba dabba doo.
圈圈你个叉叉 混球
Mishy gishy gushy gushy mishy meshy mushy, motherfucker.
黑仔 你不可能跑过半个地球
Negro, you cannot travel halfway around the world...
却连他妈的半句英语都不会说吧
and not speak any motherfucking English.
英语 混球!
English, motherfucker!
两个失踪 剩下的都不说人话
Two missing, and the rest ain't saying shit we can understand.
我正想跟你们说
I tried to tell you,
你们要问的问题呢
with the questions you all are asking.
我们下船就能再度听到英语了 对吧
We step off ship, English is once again heard, right?
差不多吧
Pretty much, yeah.
这是Osman的遗留物
Here's what's left of Osman.
他从Trieste港开始就跟我们一起
He was with us since Trieste.
Choksey跳船时带走了他所有衣物
Choksey took all his gear when he jumped.
你遇过很多跳船的人?
You get a lot of guys jumping ship?
几个吧
Some.
通常是在付过工资后  这次在Norfolk港
Usually after a pay, which we made in Norfolk.
Choksey倒是要求过预支 我们也确实会给临时代金券
Choksey actually asked for an advance, which we did using ship's scrip.
这里没有身份证明或钱 至少他把那些带走了
Nothing here in the way of ID papers or money. He grabbed that at least.
你们在海上时 还有谁要求过预支?
Anybody else ask for any advances while you were at sea?
- 比平常多 - 是吗
- More than usual. - Yeah?
有一些会日复一日过来 打更多白条
A few of them were coming back day after day, scripting more and more cash.
我们推测他们在货舱里赌博
We figured they were gambling down in the holds.
也可能不是 对吗
And maybe not, right?
那个装女孩的集装箱就在9区底层靠外
The can with the girls was in Bay 9 on the bottom, outside.
- 那区你查过了? - 查过了
- Did you check that bay? - I did.
都是出口的集装箱 在Hampton锚地装货
It's full of cans for export, loaded in Hampton Roads.
除了一堆新集装箱 没什么可疑迹象
No sign of anything except a fresh stack of containers.
警官 我不会骗你们的
I'm not gonna lie to you.
就算你们把我们都扣留 再找个翻译...
If you hold us another day and bring in interpreters...
他们还是不会交代
they're still not gonna say a thing.
甲板下发生的事不外传 这是不成文的规矩
The unwritten rule is that what happens below decks stays below decks.
坐直了 Nicky  我们还有付费的客人等着呢
Sit up, Nicky, we got paying customers waiting.
Ashley 坐下
Ashley, sit down.
你觉得剪太短了?
You think I cut it too short?
别让我看着搞笑就行
Just don't make me look funny.
Ashley的幼儿园来电话了
Ashley's preschool called.
想要更多钱?
They want more money?
只想要回我们欠的钱
Just what we owe them.
- 她的老师说... - 老师?
- And her teacher says that-- - Teacher?
- 他们不过是保姆 - 随便
- They ain't nothing but baby-sitters. - Whatever.
Ashley在班里谈起她父母不住在一起
Ashley's been talking in class about how Mom and Dad don't live together.
谁问她这个了
Who asks her about that?
没人问啊 她就是说了
No one asks, she just talks.
孩子们对这些事很敏感 总会聊的 知道吗
Kids notice stuff like that. They talk, you know?
等她上了小学 这就会是个麻烦了
By the time she's in elementary school, it's going to be an issue.
等她那么大 我们就生活在同一屋檐下了
Time she gets that far, we'll be under the same roof.
去年圣诞你也这么说
You said that last Christmas.
上帝 Aimee 你是在剪头发还是在拔头发
Christ, Aimee! You pulling it out or cutting it?
听着 Nicky
Listen, Nicky.
你想去更好的地方 我跟你
You want to go get to someplace better, I'm with you.
你想继续这样 我就得重新考虑了
You wanna keep on like this, then I got to rethink stuff.
你爱怎样怎样
Do what you feel.
一旦我拿到更多工时 头件事就是找个自己的家
As soon as I start getting more hours, the first thing I do is get my own place.
你要搬进来跟我住 很好
You wanna move in with me, great.
你要不想 那至少我它妈的尽力了
You don't want to, at least I did my goddamn best.
你想来个挑染什么的吗
You want a streak or something?
我能加点紫色上去
I could put a little purple in it.
是啊 那之后...
Yeah, and right after that...
我就给人舔屁股好了
I'll just go ahead and stick my tongue up some guy's ass.
整得你够呛?
Got you good, huh?
你觉得呢
You think?
不 我是说 不算吧
No, I mean, not really.
如果这证管科是你想待的地方
Not if Evidence Control is the posting you want.
- 抱歉 警督 - 去他的 不是吗
- Sorry, Lieutenant. - Fuck it, right?
至少我们办成了那案子
We brought in the case at least.
听说你去做水警了
Heard you were on the boat.
也不是那么糟
Ain't so bad.
Kima怎样了
How's Kima?
她现在搞内勤
She's inside.
财产罚没科
Asset Forfeiture.
她还是法律预科二年级
And she's second year pre-law.
"宅女"咯
Housecat.
不像她
That ain't her.
- 东西送回来了? - 对
- This coming back? - Yeah.
Gant案开庭在即
It's the Gant case right there.
Nathan过了一遍我们的薄弱环节...
Nathan looked over our weak shit...
让我这周去找Omar 否则她就放弃起诉
told me to go find Omar this week or she drops charges.
- 你跟他最近还有联系? - 完全没消息
- You got a line on him lately? - I haven't a clue.
我最后做的就是把他送上去纽约的公车
Last thing I did was put him on a bus to New York.
你保持低调 警督
You keep your head low, Lieutenant.
一两年后 你又会是他们的最爱了 对吗
A year or two, you'll be back in their favor, right?
一两年后 我就是个律师了
Year or two, and I'll be a lawyer.
我干了22年 这周就提交辞呈
I got 22 years in. I'm putting the papers in this week.
你要走了?
You're gone?
拿着法律学位 我还留在这鬼地方干什么?
What the hell am I doing down here with a law degree, right?
你保重 McNulty
You take care, McNulty.
你也是
You, too.
Kimmy 我想说的是 如果你 停止点那狗屁东西...
Kimmy, all I'm trying to say is, if you'd stop lighting up all the damn time...
- 也许你会明白... - 不管怎样我点定了
- maybe you'd understand-- - I'm gonna light up regardless.
- 花了我们太多时间 - 你知道我爱你 但如果你...
- It took us too long. - You know I love you, but if your ass...
还不把我那些烂钱数清楚....
don't get to finishing counting all my motherfucking money....
- 靠 你知道我爱你 但去你的 - 差不多五千
- Shit, you know I love you, but damn. - Almost five.
我们干得不赖
We got them motherfuckers good.
我们等那些混球下次再溜号吧
Let's see them motherfuckers slip next time.
你他妈什么人
Who the fuck is you?
Omar向你们问好
Omar come a-calling.
Omar? 该死
Omar? Shit.
那黑鬼不是死了吗
Ain't that nigger dead?
听说公房区的黑鬼把他干掉了
I heard them project niggers lit him up.
不 我听说的是他们把他赶了出去
No, I heard they ran his ass up out of this town.
给我放话出去 亲爱的  Omar回来了
Spread the word, darling, Omar back.
看看Crutchfield写的"趴倒在地"
Look at the way Crutchfield spelled "prostrate." Look at it.
"前文述及的被害人'前列腺'(漏了一个"r")倒地"
"The above referenced victim was prostate on the floor."
'前列腺'倒地
"Prostate on the floor."
受害者无疑啊
That's a victim, all right.
肯定疼死了
That hurts bad.
我爱死这工作了 真的
I love this job, I do.
- 想听听费城的进展吗 警司? - 说说有猫腻的地方
- You want to hear about Philly, Sarge? - Just the dirty parts.
船那边没线索了
The ship's a dead end.
原来有尸体的集装箱货区 现在填满了新集装箱
The cargo bay that held our container is full of new boxes,
没法恢复原状了
nothing to recover there.
那些船员则用各种非英语蒙我们
And all them sailors, they lied to us in every language past English.
一群语无伦次的装腔蛋
Gibbering motherfuckers.
现在正沿海航行 拿我们当笑话说吧
Sailing up the coast right now, laughing at us.
就这样了?
Is that it?
还有两个跳船了
Two guys jumped ship.
我们会发出通报以防 他们跟此事确有联系
We'll put out teletypes in case that has anything to do with anything.
其中一个留下了他的衣物 我们扣下了
One of them left his gear, and we kept that.
对
right.
看来没什么大用嘛
Sounds like some weak-ass shit to me.
本来就是
Because it is.
嫌犯总该在船上 不是吗
But your suspect had to be on the boat, right?
但你们却让船开走了
And your boat has sailed.
Jay 你希望我们怎么做
Jay, what the fuck were we supposed to do?
扣留一艘有40个船员却说53种方言的船? 拜托
Hold the ship while we chat up a crew of 40 in 53 dialects? Come on.
不那样还能怎样
If that isn't the plan, what is?
- 警员... - Russell
- Officer.... - Russell.
我听说你作为码头巡警 与凶杀科的联系人...
I am informed that you are detailed to this case...
对本案很投入
as a liaison with the port police.
我也了解你是贵单位...
I also understand that you are the only help...
唯一派来协查的
that your department is sending.
所以?
That so?
虽然我很好制服诱惑那口...
Although there is some small charm to a woman in uniform...
但凶杀科工作都穿便衣
the fact remains we work plainclothes in Homicide.
当然我不是说要穿得很朴素
Which is not to say that the clothes need be plain.
我建议你穿套装 色调柔和的不错
For you, I would suggest some pantsuits, perhaps muted in color.
可以反衬一下Moreland警探 装模作样充律师的条纹装...
Something to offset Det. Moreland's pinstriped lawyerly affectations...
及Freamon警探简单粗犷的花呢服
and the brash, tweedy impertinence of Det. Freamon.
Rawls正盯着这案子呢
Rawls is watching on this one.
让我们至少假装找到了点狗屁线索
Let's at least pretend we got a fucking clue.
简单粗犷?
Tweedy impertinence?
- 我喜欢 - 你知道吧?
- I like that. - You know what I'm saying?
- 不在这儿 警长 - 我还没瞎 它上哪去了
- It's not here, Major. - I can see that. Where is it?
Flex小队上周二用过
The Flex Squad used it last Tuesday.
行车记录表明他们22:00将车停好...
The vehicle log says they parked it at 22:00 hours...
把钥匙归还至保管处
returning the keys to the OIC.
然后呢
And?
钥匙都在
We have the keys.
但车没了?
But not the van?
你是说分配给东南区 装备齐全 价值12万美金的...
Are you telling me that a fully equipped $1 20,000 surveillance van...
监控车就这么不翼而飞了?
assigned to the southeastern district cannot be located?
- 环游世界.... - 880天
- Around the world.... - In 880 days.
我们有计划吗
Do we have a plan?
计划?
A plan?
针对Sobotka
For targeting this guy, Sobotka.
不知道
I don't know.
也许弄清他工会的活动区域...
Maybe find out where his union hangs...
带一两个线人去诱捕
go down there with a CI or two, make some hand-to-hands.
窃听他的电话怎么样
How about some DNRs on his phones?
窃听?
DNRs?
看看他跟谁通话 找出些模式
See who he's calling, and look for any kind of pattern.
暂时先搞实地诱捕吧
Hand-to-hands for now, I think.
600系列 就是那个
600 series, and that's it.
没错
That's right.
这小区对一个狱警而言也住得太好了
This is too nice a block for a prison guard.
靠 你付我再多钱我也不进监狱工作 伙计
Shit, you couldn't pay me enough to work in no prison, man.
嗯 对 不 我要你把手机股都出手
Yeah, right, no. I want you to drop all the cellular joints.
对 全部 诺基亚 摩托罗拉
Yeah, all of them, Nokia, Motorola.
看Stringer玩转华尔街
Listen to Stringer play Wall Street.
好 搞定通知我
All right, so call me, yeah.
String 你怎么这么不看好电话公司啊 伙计?
String, why you so down on the phone companies, man?
不久前我在平房区闲逛
While back, I took a stroll through the Pit.
见到了负责那区的孩子Poot
I saw that kid we got running things down there, Poot.
我给他干活用的手机插在屁股兜里...
He got the cell phone I gave him for the business, right there on his hip...
但那小子还有部专门泡妞的手机
but the nigger got another cell phone that only ring when the pussy called.
如果连这么个小虾米都能有两部手机...
Now, if this no-count nigger got two cell phones...
你他妈还想往哪儿卖这些破烂啊
how the fuck you gonna sell any more of them motherfuckers?
这叫市场饱和
That's market saturation.
看看
Look here.
Tilghman来了
That Tilghman right there.
- 穿得就像个狱警 - 看见了
- Dressed like a prison guard and all. - Yeah, I see him.
铁门
Steel door.
只有一个坐在台阶上的小子
The boy on the step is all, though.
Stump坐在窗前盯着台破电视
Stump is sitting in the front room window, staring at the damn television.
从台阶上就能看到?
You all could see that from the step?
东西在他的抽屉里
There in his damn drawers.
别叫了 死狗!
Shut up, dog!
老鼠抵达垃圾堆 有望平安回家
Rat make that trash, he home free.
Junk最好跟紧点 如果他想有所斩获的话
Junk better get in closer if he want a shot at him.
我20美元压老鼠先生 有人跟吗
I got $20 on Mr. Rat. Anyone fade me?
前进 加油 进去
Move along. Come on, get there.
100美元赌还有好戏
$100 says it ain't over.
靠 这快钱赚定了
Shit, I got to take easy money.
搞什么
What the fuck?
混球
Motherfucker.
看样子有胜负了
Sounds about over now, though.
你他妈怎么会知道老鼠要干嘛的?
How the hell you know what the rat gonna do?
Junk确实很了解这些鼠害
Junk do know his varmints.
嗯
Yeah.
你怎么了 小子?
What's wrong with you, boy?
听着 我之前也说过 伙计
Look, I done told you before, man.
那俩宝贝我还看不上眼
Those two babies don't move me that way.
如果我能想出个不用她们 就能搞定Stump的计划...
If I come up with a plan to do Stump without them...
你会跟她们散伙吗
you cut them loose?
你要帮我支招?
Now you gone and got strategic on me?
我们都喜欢像上次那样守株待兔
We do like last time, and wait for him to come out.
唯一的问题是 Stump 躲在那个老鼠洞里 宝贝
Only problem is, Stump live in that rat hole, baby.
他是不会把钱拿出来的
So, he ain't got to bring the cash out.
明白我的意思吗
See what I'm saying?
那我们就冲进去 乱枪扫射
Then we charge in, guns a-blazing.
钢制的门 对吧
Steel door, right?
你怎样才肯相信 伙计?
What's it gonna take for you to be convinced, man?
我可不会哄"小孩"
I don't bag no babies.
你觉得呢
What you think?
你得更给力点
You gonna have to do better than that.
没错
Indeed.
7克 该量以上可以定罪
我在想 如果不算太多 这次来四分之一盎司
Thinking, maybe do a quarter this time, if it's not too much.
有问题吗
That a problem?
没有
No.
我只是说 你回来得真快
I'm just saying, you back right quick with it.
那帮混球也没别的可干 对吧
It ain't like them motherfuckers got anything else to do up in there, right?
那是每天的必须品 伙计
The shit is everyday, man.
听起来是那样 钱数对吗
Sounds right. It count right, too?
那小鬼会在外面把东西给你
Boy'll bring it to you outside.
Tilghman来了
There's Tilghman.
这么说他的东西来自Butchie?
So, his shit coming from Butchie then?
好吧
All right.
大话Butchie
Lying Butchie.
圣诞老人的精灵很矮
Santa's elves are short.
圣诞老人的精灵不是真的
Santa's elves aren't real.
指环王里的才是真精灵
The elves in Lord of the Rings are, like, real elves.
真精灵?
Real elves?
那他们就该矮
They should be short, then.
矮人很矮 霍比特人很矮
Dwarves are short, hobbits are short.
精灵高且永生
Elves are tall and immortal.
如果你不是因为太害怕而不敢看电影 你现在就该搞清楚了 蠢货
If you weren't too scared to watch the movie then you'd know all about it, doofus.
你能把我怎样 傻冒
Bite me, dickbreath.
Sean 别吵了
Sean, knock it off.
他先开始的
He started it.
好了 马上上楼 刷牙 换睡衣
Okay, upstairs right away, brush your teeth, pajamas.
明天还要上课 Sean
It's a school night, Sean.
我能去给他们掖被子吗?
Can I tuck them in?
我的律师会给你寄些东西
My lawyer's gonna be sending you something in the mail.
开玩笑吧?
You're kidding.
不是离婚 只是个协议
It's not a divorce, it's an agreement.
分居协议
A separation agreement.
分居协议?
A separation agreement?
你先读读 好吗 为了我们俩
Just read it. Okay? It's for the both of us.
是为了保护我们
It's to protect the both of us.
为了什么
This is about what?
不过是....
It's just....
你只要看看就好 行吗
You should just read it, okay?
行
Okay.
又是一个打卡上班 却一无所获的一天
Another goddamn day we put our cards up and get nothing.
Zig 我都不知道还纠结个屁
Zig, I don't know why I fucking bother.
是啊 还用你说
Yeah, tell me about it.
今天一艘船 昨天没有
One ship today, nothing yesterday.
等到周四 还能来几条船...
Wait for Thursday, a couple ROIROs hit the berth...
普天他妈的同庆 能拿到一天工时
and congratu-fucking-lations, you grab a day.
到周五又无所事事了
Friday's quiet again.
这样看吧 至少你又休了一天假
Look at it this way, you know, at least you get the day off.
最不爽的就是休假 Zig
Days off is the fucking point, Zig.
我不能过着每天早起都 不知道是否有钱拿的生活
I can't keep waking up in the morning not knowing if I'm gonna get paid.
我有孩子 对吧 我他妈的有个孩子...
I got a kid, right? I got a fucking kid...
看在上帝的份上 还有个催着结婚的女友
and a girl that wants to get married, for Christ's sake.
你他妈的没事干想结什么婚
What the fuck you wanna get married for?
没说我想
Not saying I do.
妈的即使想结 也连个厕所都没有
But fuck if I even could, without no pot to piss in.
Aimee老问"有什么计划" 知道吗
Aimee is like, "What's the plan," you know?
而我在这只能整天考虑 能不能拿到一两天工时
And I'm down here wondering if I'm gonna get a day or two.
Aimee的妹妹和Petie分手了 对吧
Aimee's sister broke up with Petie, right?
你问题就在这 Zig 至少是其中之一
That's your problem, Zig, one of them, anyway.
你老用下半身思考
You let that thing of yours lead you around.
你也知道我啦 威士忌 老二 还有早上五点的勃起
You know me, whiskey, cock, and 5:00.
- 离我远点 - Nicky 听着
- Just get off me. - Nicky, look.
如果你担心的是钱 操蛋
If it's money that you're worried about, shit.
我们就一起去弄一笔
Let's pool a few dollars together.
我可以弄点可卡因来卖 你知道...
I'll get us hooked up with a little llello, you know...
早上弄 午餐前就能赚上一笔...
turn it around this morning, we make more money before lunch...
那我们一周都不用来了
than we can down here all week.
我可不想像公房区那些 操蛋黑鬼一样为点零花钱...
I ain't standing out on no corner like some fucking project nigger...
站在街角等人爆头
so that I get popped for pocket change.
去他妈的毒品 Zig
Fuck that shit, Zig.
我说真的
Seriously.
那你想做什么
What are you gonna do?
会有办法的
I'll think of something.
11900在那
1 1900 on that one.
根据货单 我们要找14580
We're looking for 14580, by the manifest.
不可能 数字没那么大
Can't be, the numbers don't go that high.
你得明白这就是港口的运作模式
You had to figure it'd be this way, the way the port works.
哦?
Yeah?
要走私有违禁品的集装箱...
Why have anything other than fake companies...
有什么比清单上的空头公司更方便
and addresses on the manifest if you're moving a can with contraband?
另一头也可能一样 对吧
And on the other end, too, right?
你可以通过海关查 但更可能...
You can work it back through customs, but chances are...
这箱子不会到这个法国Le Havre的...
this box wasn't picked up anywhere near this Rue de Rivoli address...
Rue de Rivoli手中
in Le Havre, France.
该死 也许那根本就没Rue de Rivoli
Hell, there might not even be a Rue de Rivoli in that town.
一个不知从哪来送哪去 的装满女尸的集装箱
A can full of dead girls, sent to nowhere from nowhere.
他给我带来了不少生意
He been good business for me, though.
- 哦? - 是的
- Yeah? - yeah.
一周卖四分之二 四分之三盎司
Two, three quarters a week.
Tilghman先生总是按时交钱 钱数也对
Mr. Tilghman's money always right, always on time.
所以我们才来找你安排
That's why we coming to you for the setup.
- 你是他的上家 - 我都说了
- You the man to him. - I'm just saying.
我知道 钱嘛 你知道我们会补偿你的
I know, the money, and you know we gonna find a way to make that right.
但就像我说的 我不是为自己开口
But like I said, I'm not asking for myself.
我是为我的人在开口
Now I'm asking for my man.
- Avon的意思? - 要不也不会在这了
- Avon's call? - Wouldn't be here otherwise.
- Avon就是Avon - 总是如此
- Avon is Avon. - Always.
他明天可能会过来
He probably gonna roll past tomorrow.
那就行了
That'll work.
你知道我在说什么对吧
You see what I'm saying, right?
不可能大老远的把那些女孩带来杀掉
It makes no sense to bring the girls all this way and then kill them.
你用尽办法把案子塞给了上司 自己却烦恼起来了
You go all that way to dump it on your boss, and now you're worrying yourself.
我老想着这案子
It's got me thinking is all.
晚了点 McNulty
It's a little late for that, McNulty.
那个死在河里的女孩 跟其他女孩有什么联系
What connects the one girl in the water with all the other ones in the can?
- 如果你是对的 她不是本地人 那... - 她绝对不是本地人
- If you're right and she isn't local, then-- - She's definitely not local.
补牙的混合物中较低的水银粘性...
The low level of mercury viscosity...
表明她是东欧人
in the amalgam restorations says Eastern Europe.
- 你说是就是吧 - 相信我 她不是Dundalk(爱尔兰)来的
- If you say so. - Trust me, she's not from Dundalk.
东欧?
Eastern Europe?
能再缩小点范围吗
Can you narrow it down some?
这个怎么样
How's this?
其中三个去年某个时刻 去过匈牙利的Budapest
Three of the dead girls were in Budapest, Hungary sometime last year.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know that?
她们在那整了胸
They bought tits there.
三个女孩隆了乳
Three of the girls had breast enhancements.
尸检过程中发现了袋子
We looked at the bags during the post.
我们抽出了标签和序列号...
We pulled the lot and serial numbers...
它们同属Budapest的一家整形外科诊所
and they trace back to an outpatient plastic surgery clinic in Budapest.
打过电话给那边吗
Would you call them?
可能从患者记录中查到身份
Might pull an ID from patient records.
他们能告诉我的就是植入物是今年秋的
The best they could tell me is the implants were used some time this fall.
三个女孩 三个手术 同一诊所 对吗
Three girls, three surgeries, same clinic, right?
- 还有什么? - 还有什么?
- What else? - What else?
- 去你的 Jimmy McNulty - 好了 你他妈的就是上帝
- Fuck you, Jimmy McNulty. - Okay, you're a fucking god.
这一行没人及得上你 Frazier医生
There's no one in the game who can stand in your light, Dr. Frazier, sir.
你必须得承认追查到 Budapest真他妈的磨人
You have to admit that whole Budapest thing was a hell of a pull.
这家伙的记录在哪
Where's the paperwork on this cat?
我摆在那儿了
I got it over here.
继续 还有什么
So go on, what else?
没什么了 除了棉签检测 表明至少七个箱中女孩...
Not much, except the swabs show that at least seven of the girls in the box...
在死前24小时内有过阴道性交
had vaginal intercourse within 24 hours of death.
同时 两个在肛门 六个在口腔检测呈阳性
Two had anal and six came back positive on the oral.
你跟Cole说过了?
You tell Cole about all this?
我把报告给凶杀科发过去了 但案子不是Cole在管 哥们
I sent the findings off to Homicide, but Cole ain't on the case, brother.
- 是谁? - 你朋友Bunk
- No, who is? - It's your man, Bunk.
还有另一个老家伙 他搭档 他们接了
And that older guy, his partner, they ate it.
谢了
Thanks.
我说过会给你买汽水
I told you, I brought you a soda.
好多了?
That better?
看着我 别让小男生看见你哭
Now, look at me. Don't let those mean boys see you crying.
- 好吗? - 好的
- Okay? - Okay.
我会照顾你的
I'll take care of you.
Stump先生
Mr. Stump!
Stump
Stump!
Stump先生
Mr. Stump!
那些男孩子又戏弄Chantelle了
Them boys been teasing Chantelle again.
你知道的
You know it.
- 早上好 - 早上好
- Morning. - Morning.
Bobby 最近可好?
Bobby, how you been?
不坏
Not bad.
今天做外层?
Working the tier today?
嗯 J区
Yeah, on J.
- 祝好运 - 嗯 你也是
- Have a good one. - Yeah, you, too.
高兴了 贱人?
You happy now, bitch?
我怎么知道Landsman会换下Cole 让你们上
How was I gonna know Landsman would pull Cole and stick you guys?
你跟他们一起干?
You right here with them?
- 他怎么说的Cole? - "殃及池鱼"
- What did he call Cole? - "Collateral damage."
我得说 我也觉得很"受伤"
I'm feeling pretty damn collateral myself, I got to say.
所以我才去见Frazier医生 得出点结论
Which is why I went to see Dr. Frazier and work some things out in my head.
McNulty警员本不用操心这案子 但非也
Officer McNulty could've paid this thing no mind, but no.
他朋友在受难时 他的心也在流血
When his friends are suffering, he bleeds, too.
你们看了初步尸检报告了吗
Did you see the preliminary?
阴道 肛门 口腔检测阳性
Positives for oral, vaginal, anal.
没身份证 护照 签证 钱
No IDs, no passports, no visas, no real money.
她们就这么乘船过来了
And they're coming across the water like that.
对
Yeah.
McNulty有个理论
McNulty has a theory.
现在有吗
Does he now?
你个推理狂
You deductive motherfucker, you.
所以他就在这闲逛 满嘴迟到的屁话...
So he's gonna wander in here with some Johnny-come-lately bullshit...
这些女孩如何如何被带来做妓女...
about how these girls are all coming over here as prostitutes...
说着她们是如何如何穷 只有搭集装箱偷渡...
talking about how if they ain't got the cash to travel better than a container ship...
那她们肯定没钱做整形手术
then they sure don't have the money for a plastic surgeon.
然后他就会谈及那个水中的女尸...
Then he's gonna say something about that one in the water...
她被打死然后被扔出船外
being tossed off the ship after she's already dead from a beat-down.
但她为什么会被打?
But why she got beat?
他会问我们 好像我们不知道一样
He's gonna ask us that, like we don't know.
他会自问自答 说她的棉签检测阴性 对吧
He's gonna answer his own question, saying her swabs are negative, right?
被那些水手玩弄还是反抗 她选择了后者 对吧
Fuck or fight with all them sailor boys, and she fought.
然后 来了硬的
So, it got a little rough.
她被一顿毒打 然后死了
She gets banged around, she comes up dead.
接着某人慌了
And then somebody panics,
在船靠岸前把她扔进了运河
tosses her in the harbor overnight before the ship ties up.
但其他女孩看见了
But the other girls saw.
这时这些女孩被命令返回集装箱
So now, the other girls, they get told to get back in that can.
而我们的凶手 为了掩盖这破事...
And our man, to cover this shit up...
他爬到集装箱上 堵死了通风口
he gets up on top and bangs down the air pipe.
你还有什么要告诉我们的吗
Anything else you want to tell us?
你们怎么想出来的
When did you guys get there?
昨天 船上的大副告诉我们还在海上时...
Yesterday, when the ship's first mate told us that while the ship was at sea...
半数的船员要求预付薪水
half the crew came to him for advances on their salary.
要么他们在货舱赌博...
They had one hell of a dice game going on below deck...
要么他们把集装箱的女孩弄了出来
or the boys popped them girls out of that can.
跟船员谈过了?
You talk to the crew?
- 用哪国话 - 犯罪现场找到了吗
- In what language? - Crime scene?
没有
Nope.
有人失踪吗
Anybody missing?
两人跳船了 一个在费城 一个在Norfolk
Two guys jumped ship. One in Philly, one in Norfolk.
但显然那种事常有
But that shit happens all the time, apparently.
你有得查了
Got yourself a hell of a case.
它妈的真托了你的福
Fuck you very much.
知道如果不查清楚那些女孩身份 她们会怎么样吗
You know what happens to all the girls if you don't ID them?
解剖台上的医用躯体
Anatomy Board as medical cadavers.
接着进火葬场
Then a crematorium.
最后是Crownsville的乱葬岗
Then that mass grave out at Crownsville.
那让你不爽?
That bothers you?
嗯 有点
Yeah, a little.
我也是
Me, too.
谢谢你主持这个 神父
Thanks for hosting this, Father.
希望能帮上忙
Hope it helps.
你们这次办得很用心啊
You guys have really done the background on this.
比码头工会近几年的表现都要好
This is more presence than the port unions have shown in years.
州长听到了吗
Is the governor listening?
只有一次机会
It's now or never for us.
不只是粮食码头 还有疏通河道
And not just the grain pier, but with the dredging.
我才不管工程师学会的研究怎么说
I don't care what the Corps of Engineers' study says.
- 事实上... - 打扰 Bobby
- The fact remains-- - Excuse me, Bobby.
我需要他到别的地方处理点事
I just need him to work the other side of the room on something.
你在浪费时间
You're wasting time here.
Bobby是7区的 在河中段...
Bobby's District 7, which is middle river...
因此他的每张选票 都会投给跟港口有关的人
which means every vote he gets is somebody with some port connection.
不管我们下什么功夫 总有他的票
He's a good vote, no matter what we do.
你要去做公关的...
The guys you need to be working are the guys...
是那些我们不给钱就不会帮忙的人
who wouldn't have come if we hadn't been throwing money at them.
比如说谁
Like who?
比如Anne Arundel的John Carney
Like John Carney, from Anne Arundel.
Montgomery的Liz Tobin
Liz Tobin, from Montgomery.
西区的Clay Davis
Clay Davis, from over Westside.
留住他们 你的项目就有预算了
Keep hold of them, some of your stuff stays in the budgets.
他们会支持我们?
And they're with us?
Carney是坚定支持者
Carney is pretty firm.
如果环保人士不找上她 Liz也会支持
Liz will stay solid if the environmentalists don't get to her.
Clay Davis...
这家伙 你可要死缠烂打到最后
that guy, you wanna make sure you're the last man out of the room.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我是说 我们已经给了西区民主党四万...
I mean, we've given forty large to the Westside Democratic Organization...
这混蛋还是不停地伸手
and this motherfucker still has his hand out.
我们已经给了他四万?
We spent $40,000 on that guy?
如果他让你的工程通过审查就值了
Worth it, if he lets your projects sail through the conference committee.
他妈的四万?
Forty fuckin' thousand?
我是你的说客? 你有付过钱给我吗
Am I your lobbyist? Are you paying me?
相信我
Trust me.
有房中这些人的支持...
With the players in this room...
主持官员和州长办公室的一些小帮助...
the presiding officers and a little help from the governor's office...
这次会议我们应该能尝到点甜头
we might squeeze some things out this session.
现在 去示好吧
Now, go make nice.
Davis参议员
Senator Davis.
失陪
Excuse me.
嘿 伙伴
Hey, partner.
人们都说今年港口前景不错
People tell me it just might be a good year for the port.
可能会
Might be.
你们在各方面都进步很快
You all have been stepping up in a lot of ways.
继续努力吧
Hope it continues like that.
你们在到处结交朋友 是吧?
You all making friends in a lot of places?
我们很友善
We're friendly guys.
这么说他们是凶手?
So they came back murders?
我承认我完全看不出来
I admit, I didn't see that coming at all.
谁看得出来
Who could've seen that?
无论那批女孩是谁带来的 净亏百万
For whoever was having these girls brought over the net loss is in the millions.
那么多?
That much?
只要一个女孩在东岸的俱乐部里坐台...
One of these girls on the circuit, going club-to-club on the East Coast...
两年内就能收入数十万
can bring in half a million over the next two years.
这还只是俱乐部工作和卖淫的收入
And that's just for club work and prostitution.
- 这么说某人搞砸了 - 砸得严重了
- So somebody messed up. - In a big way.
你们要的
You guys called it.
Le Havre那边没这个地址
No such address in Le Havre.
或是Brittany的任何地方
Or for that matter, anywhere in Brittany.
签载货单的司机的名字和身份证...
The name and ID of the driver who signed the bill of lading...
与机动车数据库中的记录不符
doesn't correspond to their motor vehicle database.
又是个死胡同
Dead ends either way.
那些女孩 她们知道自己来这边做什么吗
The girls, they know what they're coming over for?
有些知道
Some do.
有些会被骗说跳舞 或做秘书
Some get told they're gonna dance, or be secretaries.
要知道 她们来自并不富裕的地方
You gotta understand, they're coming from places that don't have much.
罗马尼亚 摩尔达维亚 俄罗斯 阿尔巴尼亚
Romania, Moldavia, Russia, Albania.
约有4到5万无签证妇女在美国工作
40,000 or 50,000 undocumented women working in the US alone.
5万? 上帝啊
50,000? Jesus.
得另成立个部门管理她们
They need a whole new agency just to police them.
她们需要的是个工会
What they need is a union.
- 敬Stan和Kate - Stan和Kate
- To Stan and Kate. - Stan and Kate.
结婚纪念快乐
Happy anniversary!
非常感谢
Thanks a lot.
- 过得很愉快? - 是的
- Good time here? - Yeah.
我的案子怎么样了
How is my detail coming?
Grayson警督很不错 对吗
Lt. Grayson is on top of things, right?
Burrell推荐他
Burrell recommended him.
说他很擅长查资产犯罪
Said he was really good at property crimes.
- 那得花点时间 - 你觉得?
- It's gonna take a while. - You think?
为什么 你们都查到什么了
Why? What are you doing?
不多
Not much.
我们没有监听 也没在查任何工会资产
We got no DNRs up. We're not looking at any union assets.
也没收集到任何航运检验标签之类的
We're not collecting tag numbers or anything.
我们根本就没在查犯罪模式 什么都没有
We're not looking for patterns at all. And that's the thing.
我一直想跟你说Barksdale案的办案方式
I'm trying to tell you about the Barksdale thing.
你得明白旁敲侧击...
If you go in with the idea you're gonna eat around the edges...
就永远命中不了红心
you never get a meal.
对付Barksdale Daniels 和Freamon用上了所有手段
With Barksdale, Daniels and Freamon had us pulling all kinds of stuff.
车管所记录 电话记录 公司执照等...
DMV records, phone logs, corporate charter stuff...
政治捐款
political campaign contributions.
如果Burrell不这么快结案...
If Burrell didn't break the case down so fast...
我们可能已经查了价值3到4百万的市中心房产了...
we would've brought back $3 or $4 million in downtown real estate...
更不用提他们捐的政治献金了
not to mention the money those guys gave to political campaigns.
我们查得很彻底 相当彻底
We were deep, really deep.
我一直想告诉你来着
I've been trying to tell you.
如果不是Burrell 那会成为一个要案
If it wasn't for Burrell, that would've been a major case.
String
String.
你知道 我只是过来看看
You know, I just came to check up on you.
看你过得如何
See how you holding it down.
还不错
I'm all right.
- 小家伙呢 - 刚睡下
- Where the little man at? - I just put him down.
你想喝点什么
You want something to drink?
D'Angelo知道他失去了什么吗
Do D'Angelo know what he's missing?
我想他肯定知道
I'm sure he do.
你倒是提醒了我
You just reminded me about something.
商标还在呢
Tag's still on it.
他在Jersey被捕前买的
He bought it before he got stopped in Jersey.
还没来得及穿
Never been worn.
你知道 浪费就是犯罪
You know, it's a shame to let things go to waste.
你知道 你能扔掉男人的衣服...
You know, you can give away the man's clothes...
但没法让他们消失 不是吗
but that don't make him gone, right?
我没忘记他
I ain't forget him.
但也没怎么去看过他
You ain't been to see him much neither, though.
- 最近不怎么好过 - 不好过?
- It's been hard. - It's been hard?
他也不怎么好过
It's been hard on him, too.
一个人被关进去就会想很多乱七八糟的事
A lot of bad things caught up in a man's head when he's on lock-down.
他需要看到孩子他妈
Man need to see his baby mama.
还有他孩子
Need to see his child, too.
他需要借此安心 否则...
Only one thing he needs to be secure about, and if not...
他会觉得自己无法忍受那刑期...
then he might start thinking he can't do that time...
到时我们就麻烦了
and then we all got problems.
你明白了?
You understand me?
你在这没困难吧
How you set here?
房子 车 钱都没问题?
The apartment, the car, the money's all right?
都好
It's good.
都好?
It's good?
我知道都好
I know it's good.
但你知道我在说什么 对吗
But you know what I'm talking about, right?
我们都有自己的事做 你的任务 就是让D'Angelo知道我们还是一家
We all got a job to do, and your job is to let D'Angelo know we still family.
那很重要
It's important.
我的尺码是XL
I'm an XL.
毫无疑问
No doubt.
- 到你了 Jimmy - 上帝
- Your round, Jimmy. - Jesus.
如果我现在不闪...
I'm gonna owe the baby-sitter half my salary...
就得把一半的薪水送给保姆了
if I don't throw myself out of here right now.
- 你有孩子? - 两个
- You got kids? - Two.
老爸也工作到很晚?
Daddy working late, too?
他可从来没有过
Not a day in his goddamn life.
你不用付
You barely made a dent.
晚安 先生们
Good night, gents.
- 晚安 - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
- 什么情况 - 不知道
- What's that about? - I don't know.
告诉你我要干什么
Tell you what I'm gonna do.
- 解决这该死的案子? - 才不
- Solve the fucking case? - Not a shot.
- 我要给她取个名 - 取名?
- I'm gonna give this one a name. - A name?
她不会被葬在Crownsville
She's not going out to Crownsville, this one.
我查就不会
Not on me, she's not.
那你想怎么做
So what are you gonna do with her?
买个棺材 办个葬礼  再送回欧洲的某个鬼地方?
Pay for a box and a mortician and ship her back to Bumfuck, Europe?
不 我要找到她的亲友
No, I'm gonna find where her people at.
那有什么关系 这算是天主教那套吗 Jimmy
How does that matter? You see, this is that Catholic shit, Jimmy.
这是祭坛男孩的忏悔
This is that little altar-boy-guilt talking.
我他妈有什么好忏悔的
What the fuck I got to feel guilty about?
我算算
Let me count the ways.
早上好 警长
Good morning, Major.
我靠....
What the....
Wilmington? 狗娘养的
Wilmington? Son of a bitch!
Frank?
Ring 最近如何?
Ring, how's it hanging?
不咋地
Not so good.
- 至少现在如此 - 是吗
- Not right now. - Yeah?
我会费迟交了 你知道 对吧
I'm late on my dues. You know that, right?
你迟交了 对
You're late, yeah.
还有我把那破别克停在离家两个街区外
And I'm parking that piece-of-shit Buick two blocks from the house...
希望收破烂的手脚别太勤快
hoping for a lazy repo man.
有那么糟?
That bad?
我知道你拿不到工时 进展有点慢
I know you ain't been getting hours, it's been slow.
上月只做了五天
Five days last month.
- 就这么点 - 就这么点?
- That's all. - Is that all?
听着 我要么饿死要么只能离开了
Look, I got to shit or get off the pot here.
- 我要去47分会 - 行行好
- I'm gonna go with 47. - Do me a favor.
Frank 你很公正 我不会说你不公正
Frank, you been fair, I ain't saying otherwise.
只是我前面还有六十个比我资格老的
It's just there's 60 checkers above me with more seniority, and that's all she wrote.
帮帮忙 今晚到Clement街...
Do me a favor. Go down Clement Street tonight...
把钱给Dolores 告诉她 你要来杯啤酒 我请
give this to Dolores, tell her you need a beer and a shot on me.
- Frank 我... - 就帮我这个忙
- Frank, I... - Just do that much.
我请客 喝完回家
You have a round on me, you go home.
你明天如果还过来告诉我 你想去47分会 我随你
You wanna come in tomorrow, tell me you're going with 47, I'm with you on it.
谢谢
Thanks.
4号车道 获知车牌
Lane 4, you got a trucker's code and tag.
帮我挑一个 Johnny
Pick me a winner, Johnny.
你丑得真适合开卡车
You're ugly enough to be a teamster.
咬我啊 贱货
Lick me, you whore.
即将上车 K排 122号位
It'll be up on wheels. K-row, slot 1 22.
收到
Roger that.
看 错误交付
Look, misdelivery.
本该在Norfolk上岸的集装箱
Can was supposed to go ashore at Norfolk.
嗯 你想搁哪儿?
Yeah, where you want it?
我想在K-122装车
I'm gonna need it on wheels at K-1 22.
我的人会在那收货的
My man'll pick it up there.
谢了 Horse
Thanks, Horse.
送错的集装箱
Wrong box, misdelivery.
不用数了 Butch
No need to count, Butch.
- 我向来够数 - 听
- My shit always right. - Hearing.
耳听为实
Hearing is believing.
你准备好的话 小鬼会在外面等你
Boy'll meet you outside when you ready to roll.
准备好了
I'm ready now.
不 小狗 我才不给你
No, dog. Not from me you don't.
回见 Butchie
Later, Butchie.
Avon那儿没法通融了?
Your man Avon ain't got no flex.
恐怕不行
Afraid not.
你更喜欢谁
Who you like better?
终极蜘蛛侠还是普通那个?
Ultimate Spiderman or regular Spiderman?
有什么区别吗
What's the difference?
看 我什么都得教你
See, I'll have to teach you everything.
失陪 先生们
Excuse me, gents.
怎么样了 伙计? 喜欢图书馆吗
What's up, man? How you liking the library?
不错
It'll do.
工作比较轻松
It's easy on you.
我知道很多人想要这工作 但终究还是归你了
I know a lot of people put in for the gig, but the gig go to you.
到手得多有趣
Funny how that go.
你想我对你说谢谢?
So you want me to say thanks?
你什么都不用说
You ain't got to say shit.
但你要搞清楚如果你保持头脑清楚...
But you need to take heed of what can be done for you...
你能得到什么好处
if you keep your head straight.
你真是助人为乐 不是吗
You're just full of favors, ain't you?
闭上嘴想清楚...
You shut your mouth and open your mind...
那你就只用服这20年中的一小段刑期
and you ain't gonna be doing but a small piece of this 20.
就像我只用服刑七年中的一两年一样
Just like I'm only gonna do a year or two on this seven.
明白了吗
Feel me?
我有优先考量
I got priors.
最多我只能服一半 10年 还能忍受10年
Best I can do is half. That's 10. I can count to 10.
有些事已经在办了 Dee 好吗 你好好想想
Some shit is coming down, Dee, okay? You need to think.
你得相信我 好好想清楚
You need to trust, and you need to get your head right.
伙计 我自有想法
Man, my head is where I want it.
- 你最近脸色很差 - 又怎样
- You look dusty lately. - So what?
怎么 在这里你成我妈了?
What, you my mom up in here now?
那是懦弱的人才会干的事
That's the weak man's road you're taking.
我从没见你这么懦弱过
I ain't never seen you as weak.
听着 我只是 你知道 偶尔来点
Look, I'm just, you know, every now and again.
那是唯一能让我在这屎坑保持清醒的方法
That's all I got to get my head up out of this shithole.
就没别的了? 因为如果就为那个...
Ain't no more than that? Because if that's all it is...
那你应该能停用几天
you should be able to give it a rest for a few days.
因为对你也不算什么 对吗
Because it ain't no thing, right?
对 不算什么
Yeah, it ain't no thing.
那你会吗?
Then you gonna do that?
我出于关心才问的
I'm asking you, man, out of love.
我始终在关心你 Dee
There's always love, Dee.
好吧 会的
All right. Yeah.
停几天 没问题 停几天
A few days. Sure, a few days.
好
Right.
好了 带来了什么货
All right, what have you got?
全数码的 四百万像素 16兆存储卡...
All digital. Four megapix, 16 megs of memory...
3倍光学变焦 4倍数字变焦 都是市场上的新货
3X optical, 4X digital zoom. That's brand new on the market.
这些可是相机中的凯迪拉克
That's the Cadillac of cameras right there.
- 多少 - 400
- How many? - 400.
- 那可是个大数目 - 这是个大动作 不是小打小闹
- You are talking a big number. - That's showtime. This ain't the WNBA.
我想以这性能和品牌...
I'm thinking with these features, this brand...
零售价约350美元
I can get, maybe, $350 each at retail.
- 好 成交 - 不行 不成交
- All right, cool. - Nope, not cool.
500美元
$500.
我问了些本地的连锁店
Yeah, I've been calling some of the local chain stores.
你知道 百思买 电器城
You know, Best Buy, Circuit City.
这型号要价550 特价时也要500
This model goes for $550, $500 when they're on sale.
好吧 500
Okay, $500.
- 乘以400 就是... - 二十万
- Times 400 units, that comes to-- - That's $200,000.
你想要多少
What are you looking for?
百分之二十
Twenty percent.
我们有三个人
There's three of us.
我还想要个细足踝的女人呢
I want a woman with thin ankles.
但今晚回家 看到的还是我的黄脸婆
But I'm going to go home tonight, and there's going to be my wife.
百分之八 一万六千
Eight percent. $16,000.
你和你朋友每人能拿超过5000块
That's over $5,000 apiece for you and your friends.
2万 先付清
$20,000. Upfront.
因为我喜欢你
Because I like you.
看看 温馨柯达一刻
Look at that. It's a Kodak moment in the house.
我得跟我的人商量
I got to run this by my people.
他们没问题 我会再联系你
They okay it, I'm going to give you a call.
好的 成交
All right, cool.
- 你看见了? - 嗯
- Did you see that? - Yeah.
你在侮辱我的A 你加注个鬼啊?
You gonna insult my ace, you check-and-raise piece of shit?
- 去你的 Augie 要跟就跟不跟盖牌 - 我跟 加注
- Fuck you, Augie, see it or fold. - I'll see it and raise you back.
- 说话啊 Augie - 立正
- Talk to me, Augie. - Ten-hut.
警督哪去了
Where's the lieutenant?
他街上巡逻去了
He's on the street.
我不是个政客 我连计算选票都不会
I'm not a politician. I wouldn't even know how to count votes.
也许他们知道轮到我们了
Maybe they know it's our time.
Tony
Tony.
现在叫你局长还早了吗
Too soon to call you Commissioner?
失陪一下
Excuse me one sec.
- 你调给我废物 - 警长?
- You sent me humps. - Major?
你调给我一帮废物 Ervin
You sent me a detail of humps, Ervin.
- 我们明天再谈 - 不 我想我们现在就可以谈...
- We can discuss this tomorrow. - No, I think we discuss it now...
或者我就这么过去告诉Santoni...
or I'm gonna walk in there and tell Santoni...
对这该死的加冕礼投反对票
to vote against this goddamn coronation.
还有更绝的 我会告诉一些朋友...
And more than that, I'm gonna talk some shit to some of my friends...
Barksdale案最后发生了什么
about what happened at the end of the Barksdale case.
你听明白了吗
You hear me on that?
Barksdale是一次成功的起诉
The Barksdale case was a successful prosecution.
也许到我们的人开始追查账目之前都是
Up until our people tried to chase the cash, maybe.
我相信已达到法定人数
We have a quorum, I believe.
理事会成员请就坐
Council members can take their seats now.
告诉你 副局长
Tell you what, Deputy.
你可能仍能拿到足够选票...
You probably still got enough votes...
但我能让场面变得比你想象的难看
but I can make it uglier than you want it.
你想怎么样 Stan?
What do you want, Stan?
我要一个真正的专案小组 真正的警察和组长
I want a real detail, with real police and a real unit commander.
行 可以
Fine, done.
给我办Barksdale案的那个警督
Give me that black lieutenant that did Barksdale.
Daniels已经提出辞呈 他要走了 不玩了
Daniels put in his papers. He's gone, out the door.
他去领退休金了吗?
Did he meet the pension board yet?
我建议你跟他谈谈
I suggest you talk to the man.
- 我尽力而为 - 别跟我来这套 Erv
- I'll do what I can. - Don't fuck with me, Erv.
我在这大厅里的朋友跟你一样多
I got as many friends here in the hall as you do.
而就我对Barksdale案的理解...
And with what I'm learning about the Barksdale case...
我有的是你的小辫子
I got all kinds of shit I can throw.
- 20分钟后关闭 - 好的
- Lock-down in 20. - All right.
什么事 Ice?
What's up, lce?
你看完那本绿灯侠了?
You done with that Green Lantern?
你那去看吧 但要还我
You can read it, but I want it back.
你给Dee了?
You hit Dee?
Dee不要
Dee ain't up.
400台上等相机 Spiros牌
Four hundred good cameras, Spiros.
谁带来的?
Who brought them in?
那个年轻的装卸工 Niko 还有他的白痴表弟
The young stevedore, Niko, and that idiot cousin of his.
我觉得他也在吸
And I think he uses, too.
Stefanos
Stefanos.
我他妈的毫不关心
I don't give a damn nothing about him.
我付百分之十就可以买下那些相机
Listen, I'm paying 10 cents on the dollar for the cameras.
就能净赚18万
We're going to clear $180,000.
- Niko呢 - 他很聪明
- What about Niko? - He's smart.
那就交易吧
Make the deal.
你他妈今晚怎么回事
What the hell's wrong with you tonight?
- 什么 - 你表现得太正常了
- What? - You're acting normal.
知道吗 Dolores?
You know what, Dolores?
我今天赚钱了
I made money today.
哦? 哪条船
Yeah? What ship was in?
嘿 Zig
Hey, Zig.
来杯烈酒和一杯啤酒 Dolores
Shot and a beer, Dolores.
Frank Sobotka说我得喝点
Frank Sobotka says I needed it.
谢了
Thanks.
这是什么
What's this?
找给你的 或者Frank Sobotka这么说的
Your change. Or so says Frank Sobotka.
- 真的? - 看在上帝的份上 反正不是我的
- Sure? - It ain't mine, for Christ's sake.
你不拿 别人也会拿
If you don't take it, someone else is gonna.
你爸真是个大好人 Zig
Your pop's a good man, Zig.
嘿 来这
Yo, up here!
T.C. 怎么回事
T.C., what's up?
发生什么事了
What's going on?
他们昏厥了 我看见四个
They falling out, four that I seen.
什么
What?
他妈的怎么回事?
What the fuck is going on?
东西不对 下毒了!
Bad package. Hot shots.